Securities. Please go ahead.
Oh, thank you so much. Some of your competitors are becoming increasingly vocal about extending
big LOEs at the end of the decade.
Novartis is the notable exception. It could be attributed to nothing more than communication
practices. But if Novartis feels it has a good shot at delaying Cosentix LOE, then why not note
that? And if this is an area of active pursuit, what is it that you're doing? Co-formulation,
extended dosing. And related to all this, if Karen Hale is in the room, can she compare and
contrast this to her experience at AbbVie? Thank you.
Yeah, thanks.
Thanks, Steve. So, you know, Karen Hale is in the room, but I'll spare her from having to compare
her thoughts with AbbVie. I think that would be not the appropriate setting to do that. But we
appreciate the question. I mean, of course, we have extensive efforts to defend our IP and then
look at other ways to, you know, formulate our medicines. I mean, a good example is the Cosimta
two-month, which we do have now, planned readout. We have additional efforts as well to life cycle
manage.
We have additional efforts to do the Cosimta into longer intervals as well, which are still in the,
you know, early phases of efforts. We'll see how that progresses. All of that would generate
new IP, I think. And so that one is clear. I think with Cosentix, we have a number of cell
line formulation and other patents that we continue to prosecute. We, as a practice, don't
add those in as potential scenarios until we've gotten further along, I think, in the litigation
phase to really understand where, you know, where those trials ultimately fit. So I think with
Cosentix, with Cosimta, many efforts. I think we've discussed extensively with Cascali the efforts
around CDK2, CDK2-4, the picovation efforts as well. Harder with a small molecule, as you know,
to come up with, you know, significant reformulation efforts, but something that we're
certainly looking at. I would point out, even for medicines like Semblix, we're actively already
working on with the, you know, the, you know, the, you know, the, you know, the, you know, the, you
know, the, you know, the, you know, the, you know, the, you know, the, you know, the, you know,
ways to hopefully extend that franchise even further. You know, with LifeBO, we move from
six months also to now go to 12 months and also to look at combinations of LifeBO to target other
siRNA targets within cardiovascular disease, things like HMG-CoA reductase amongst others.